Two cultures. Two women. One love.
I Can't Think Straight is a drama, romance film directed by Shamim Sarif.
Tala, a London-based Palestinian, is preparing for her elaborate Middle Eastern wedding when
she meets Leyla, a young British Indian woman who is dating her best friend.
Spirited Christian Tala and shy Muslim Leyla could not be more different from each
other, but the attraction is immediate and goes deeper than friendship.
But Tala is not ready to accept the implications of the choice her heart has made for her and escapes back to Jordan,
while Leyla tries to move on with her new-found life, to the shock of her tradition-loving parents.
As Tala's wedding day approaches, simmering tensions come to boiling point
and the pressure mounts for Tala to be true to herself.
Tala, played by Lisa Ray.
Leyla, played by Sheetal Sheth.
Reema, played by Antonia Frering.
Omar, played by Dalip Tahil.
Housekeeper, played by Nina Wadia.
Maya, played by Siddiqua Akhtar.
I Can't Think Straight is a 2008 British romantic
drama film directed by Shamim Sarif.
Based on Sarif's 2008 novel of the same name, the film tells the story of a London-based Jordanian of Palestinian descent, Tala, who is preparing for an
elaborate wedding when a turn of events causes her to have an affair, and subsequently fall in love, with another woman, Leyla, a British Indian.
The film stars Lisa Ray and Sheetal Sheth.
I Can't Think Straight was produced by Enlightenment Productions and
distributed in the United States by Regent Releasing and Here!
It was released in different regions between 2008 and 2009.
The DVD was released on 4 May 2009.
The lead actresses, Ray and Sheth, also starred in Sarif's 2007
lesbian-themed historical drama film The World Unseen.
The film explores themes of lgbt, woman director, lesbian.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.